# ANDREI KONDAKOV

# **Data Scientist**

- +36205352841 @ andreykondakov2302@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrei-kondakov-4994852b2
- Budapest, Hungary

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Data Analyst

10/2022 - Present

#### **Data Monsters**

Location

- Analyzed histories of users of the big investment company. Based on these data, I was able to identify the main symptoms that affect the future behaviour of the investors
- Created interpreted model which estimates current health of the investors and it helps sales understand what the client is happy or dissatisfied with
- Created a custom model for object tracking. Gathered dataset and trained on its model for detection and tracking based on the YOLO8 model. For data markup and training use Roboflow and UltraliticsCreated CV pipeline including tracking objects from video streams and extracting texts from them
- Created pipeline for current speaker detection and verification based on FaceNet model and Tracking model.
- After analyzing the Google Trends data, we created predictive models based on them.

#### Data Science Intern

10/2021 - 02/2022

#### BroughtonLab

Location

- Created a recommendation system for articles from the site arxiv.comImplemented following models: model for keywords extraction, text2vec model for finding articles with similar content, NER model for gathering medical naming entities from articles
- Created eye-tracking pipeline for tracking a person's gaze on the information stand screen using 3 different OpenVINO models.

# **EDUCATION**

BSc Fundamental Information technologies

01/2019 - 01/2023

Southern Federal University

Rostov-on-Don, Russia

Diploma with honor

MSc Info-Bionics Engineering

01/2023

Pázmány Péter Catholic University

Budapest, Hungary



## **SUMMARY**

I am a dedicated and driven Data Scientist with 2 years of experience in a large company, possessing extensive knowledge across various fields of data science. I am seeking a position where I can apply and further develop my professional skills.

## **SKILLS**

Algorithms ·

Computer Architecture ·

Computer Vision · Dart ·

Data Science · Github ·

Natural Language Processing ·

OpenCV · Python · Reactis ·

Typescript · C++ ·

 $Statistical\ analysis\cdot$ 

Time series analisis  $\cdot$  Research  $\cdot$ 

Computer vision

# FIND ME ONLINE

1 Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrei-kondakov-4994852b2

Github

https://github.com/AndreyKondakovGW

# **LANGUAGES**

English	Proficient
Russian	Native

